Guide to the John N. Warfield papers, 1931-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Textual Materials, 1943-2001; (51 boxes)
  - "[Correspondence: Bell Northern Research Limited]", 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - "[Correspondence: Iowa State University Press]", 1993-1996 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - "[Correspondence: China Travel Infromation, Projects]", 1993 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - [Correspondence: Defesne Systems Management College (D.S.M.C)]," Henry ALbert, 1993-1995 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - "[Correspondence: Mr. President, the White House, Washington D.C.]", 1993 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - "[Correspondence: Ghana], 1993-1996 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - "[Correspondence:Roxanna Cardenas]," Projects, 1993-1996 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - "[Correspondence:India]", 1994 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - "[Correspondence: Mr. Werner Ulrich, Switzerland]", 1993 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - "[Correspondence:Internatinoal Conferences, Projects]", 1994 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - "[Correspondence: Interactive Management, E-mail, Unsorted], 1993-1995 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - "[Correspondence: Dr. August W. Smith, Center for Interactive Management Leadership Incorporation (C.I.M.I)]", 1993-1995 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - "[Correspondence: The Institute of Public Policy (T.I.P.P)]", 1994 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - "[Correspondence: David Mackett, Photos for a Science of Generic Design]", 1993 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - "Defense Systems Management College (D.S.M.C) - Purchase Order for Software", July 24, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - "[Internal Affairs Correspondence:The Institute of Public Policy & George Mason University]", 1994 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - "National Center for Manufacturing Sciences (N.C.M.S) - Focus, Newsletter", 1994 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - "[Correspondence: England, Proposal's & Conferences], 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - "[Correspondence: Mr. Benjamin J. Broome]", 1995 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - "[Correspondence: Mr. Michael McMaster England]", 1995 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - "[Correspondence: Mr. Scott Staley, Ford Motor Company]", 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - "[Correspondence: E-mail, Unsorted, the Institute of Public Policy (T.I.P.P.), George Mason University]", 1995 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - "[Correspondence: International Conferences & Projects], 1995 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - "[Correspondence: Mr. Joe Chiara]", 1996 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - "[Correspondence: Dr. Mark Klein, Boeing], 1994 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - "[Correspondence: Roxana Cardenas, Mexico], 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - "[Correspondence: Dr. Walter Bogan Education Papers], 1993-1995 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - "Symposium: On Creativity & Innovation",Miel Pragqe Hotel, Tokyo, November 14, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - "Symposium: Productivity & Innovation," (I.T.E.S.M), Mexico, October 22, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - "[Correspondence: Dr. Don Clausing, Total Quality Development]", 1994 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - "Annotated Mathematical Bibliography for Interpretive Structural Modeling," [John N. Warfield], May 23, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - "Artificial Philosophy & the Decline of Technology," [John N. Warfield], 1992 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - "Design & Manufacturing Methodologies: A Comparison of American & Japanese Developments," Working Paper, March 23, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - "Development of End-User Access Tools to Science of Design: A Final Report," Ford Motor Company, January 1992 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - "Dwie Podstway Projectowania (Dual-Basis Design)," Polish Publication, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - "A Handbook of Interactive Management: Three Early Drafts, 1992" (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - "A Handbook of Interactive Management: Drafts, 1992" (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - "A Handbook of Interactive Management: (IASIS) Drafts, 1992" (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - "Index to Slow Speed Videotapes of First Interactive Management Workshop on Design of an Analytical Powertrain," Written by Rose Warfield, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - "Index to Slow Speed Videotapes: Copying Instructions", 1992 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - "The Learning Organization: Its Relevance to Policy-Making," [John N. Warfield], 1992 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - "The Mathematics of Modeling," Presented at ITESM, Mexico, July 27, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - "Project Experience," [John N. Warfield], June 1992 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - "So You Are a Good Modeler: Not Yet!," Short Circuit Newsletter [John N. Warfield], 1993 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - "Some Magnificent Academic Trussels & Their Social Consequences," Presented at Annual Meeting of Association for Integrative Studies (A.I.S), November 19, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - "Study Questions for Use with a Handbook of Interactive Management," [John N. Warfield], November 15, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - "Technomyopia Threatens our National Security," Revised Version [John N. Warfield], 1992 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - "Thinking in, and Not Thinking in Sets," Short Circuit Newsletter [John N. Warfield], 1992 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - "The Warfield Argentine Seminar Series," Presentation, Argentina General Systems & Cybernetics [John N. Warfield], 1992 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - "Widely -Ignored Subtleties that are Critical to Decision Making," Presentation International Conference - Multiple Criteria Decision Making (M.C.D.M), August 8, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - "A Clanthink," Lecture Presented at Bell Northern Research Limited [John N. Warfield], June 3, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - "Foundations of Thought," Notebook Pages Prepared for Mathematics of Modeling Workshop, July 1993 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - "Groupthink, Clanthink, Spreadthink & Linkthink: Decision Making on Complex Issues in Organizations," [John N. Warfield, Carol Tiegen], 1993 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - "Interactive Management Symposium," [John N. Warfield], June 1993 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - "Organizations & Structural Thinking," Short Circuit Newsletter [John N. Warfield], 1993 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - "Preguntas Dr. Warfield," An Interview of Dr. John Warfield by Roxana Cardenas of (I.T.E.S.M) Mexico, February 23, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - "Self-Study Program Development Guides for Warfield Literature: A Report," Submitted to Defense Systems Management College (D.S.M.C), December 1993 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - "She Hui Xi Tong - Ji Hua Gong Zuo (Societal Systems in Chinese)," Translation into Chinese of the Societal Systems, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - "So you Believe in X, Why?," Short Circuit Newsletter [John N. Warfield], January 23, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - "Education Papers," Volume-I Papers Written 1968-1979 [John N. Warfield] (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - "Education Papers," Volume-II Papers Written in 1980 [John N. Warfield] (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - "Education Papers," Volume-III Papers Written in 1980 [John N. Warfield], 1981 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - "Education Papers," Volume-II Written in 1980, Volume-III Papers Written in 1981 [John N. Warfield], 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - "Education Papers," Volume-IV Papers Written 1968-1979 [John N. Warfield], 1968-1996 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - "Education Papers," Volume-V Papers Written 1968-1979 [John N. Warfield], 1987-1991 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - "Education Papers," Volume IV Written 1982-1986, Volume V Papers Written in 1987-1990 & Volume VI & VII [John N. Warfield], 1982-1991 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - "Education Papers Stored on 1 GB Drive," VOLUME IV, V & VII [John N. Warfield], 1982-1991 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Series 2: Audiovisual Materials, 1978-2000; (21 boxes)
  - "Professional Schools & Great University," (IASIS) Seminar #1 [John N. Warfield, Coleman Raphael][Two Copies], October 18, 1989 (Box 52, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Five Images of the University," (IASIS) Seminar #2 [John N. Warfield, Anita Taylor][Two Copies, 1 Empty], October 30, 1989 (Box 52, Folder Audiotape)
  - "University Infrastructure & Interdisciplinary Work," (IASIS) Seminar #3 [John N. Warfield, Clara Lovett][Two Copies], November 27, 1989 (Box 52, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Designing the Great University," (IASIS) Seminar #4 [John N. Warfield, Harold Morowitz][Two Copies], February 14, 1990 (Box 52, Folder Audiotape)
  - "The University College & The Great University," (IASIS) Seminar #5 [John N. Warfield, Paula Lewis][Two copies], March 7, 1990 (Box 52, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Leadership & The Great University, (IASIS) Seminar #6 [John N. Warfield, George W. Johnson][Two Copies], April 18, 1990 (Box 52, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Preguntas, an Interview," [John N. Warfield, Roxana Cardenas [Tape 1 of 2], 1991 (Box 52, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Preguntas, an Interview," [John N. Warfield, Roxana Cardenas][Tape 2 OF 2], 1991 (Box 52, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Systems Science Program Planning Discussion, Group 1", November 13, 1989 (Box 53, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Systems Science Program Planning Discussion, Group 2", November 14, 1989 (Box 53, Folder Audiotape)
  - "John N. Warfield Discusses Systems COncepts & His Work in Systems Field", undated (Box 53, Folder Audiotape)
  - "John N. Warfield Explains Delta Chart & (I.S.M)," [John N. Warfield], undated (Box 53, Folder Audiotape)
  - "John N. Warfield & Reckmeyer Discussion", June 2, 1989 (Box 53, Folder Audiotape)
  - "John N. Warfield Class Lecture, Class Meeting Number 8, Spring Semester," Part 1, George Mason University, March 20, 1999 (Box 53, Folder Audiotape)
  - "John N. Warfield Class Lecture, Class Meeting Number 8," Part 3, George Mason University, March 20, 1989 (Box 53, Folder Audiotape)
  - "John N. Warfield Class Lecture, Class Meeting Number 9," Part 3 [Two Copies], George Mason University, March 27, 1989 (Box 53, Folder Audiotape)
  - "John N. Warfield Class Lecture, Class Meeting Number 10", George Mason University, April 3, 1999 (Box 53, Folder Audiotape)
  - "John N. Warfield Class Lecture, Class Meeting Number 12" [Tape 1 of 2], George Mason University, April 24, 1999 (Box 53, Folder Audiotape)
  - "John N. Warfield Class Lecture, Class Meeting Number 12" [Tape 2 of 2], George Mason University, April 24, 1999 (Box 53, Folder Audiotape)
  - "John N. Warfield Class Lecture, Class Meeting Number 13" George Mason University, May 1, 1999 (Box 53, Folder Audiotape)
  - "John N. Warfield Class Lecture, Class Meeting Number 14" [Tape 1 of 2], George Mason University, May 8, 1999 (Box 53, Folder Audiotape)
  - "John N. Warfield Class Lecture, Class Meeting Number 14" [Tape 2 of 2], George Mason University, May 8, 1999 (Box 53, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Warfield Lecture," [Tape 1 of 2], George Mason University, January 30, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Warfield Lecture," [Tape 2 of 2], George Mason University, January 30, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield][Tape 1 of 2], February 13, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield][Tape 2 of 2], February 13, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield][Tape 1 of 2], February 27, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield][Tape 2 of 2], February 13, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield][Tape 1 of 2], March 6, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield], March 13, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield][Tape 2 of 2], March 6, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield][Tape Copy 1 of 4], April 17, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield][Tape Copy 2 of 4], April 17, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield][Tape Copy 3 of 4], April 17, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield][Tape Copy 4 of 4], April 17, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Discovery & Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield][Tape 1 of 2], February 6, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Discovery & Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield][Tape 2 of 2], February 6, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Discovery & Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield][Tape 1 of 2], February 20, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Discovery & Complexity Lecture," [John N. Warfield][Tape 2 of 2], February 20, 1999 (Box 54, Folder Audiotape)
  - "Interactive Management," Slow Speed VHS Tapes [Tape 1 of 4], undated (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Interactive Management," Slow Speed VHS Tapes [Tape 2 of 4], undated (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Interactive Management," Slow Speed VHS Tapes [Tape 3 of 4], undated (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Interactive Management," Slow Speed VHS Tapes [Tape 4 of 4], undated (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management - Winnebago Tribes," Interview on VHS Tapes [Donna Vandall], undated (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management - Winnebago Tribes," Interview on VHS Tapes [LaDonna Harris], undated (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management - Winnebago Tribes," Interview on VHS Tapes [Reuben Snake], undated (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Building Consensus on a Winnebago Self-Sufficiency Plan," (IASIS) VHS Tape, 1987 (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Winnebago Indians," (IASIS) VHS Tape [John N. Warfield], July 30, 1987 (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management - Winnebago #1," Introduction on VHS Tape, July 30, 1987 (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management - Winnebago #2," Problem Statement on VHS Tape, July 30, 1987 (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management - Winnebago #3," Problem Solution Discussion & Flute Music on VHS Tape, July 31, 1987 (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management - Winnebago #4," Closing Out Session on VHS Tape, July 31, 1987 (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Preguntas, an Interview of John N. Warfield by Roxana Cardenas," VHS Tape [Tape 2 of 2], 1991 (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "First Interactive Management Workshop on Design of an Analytical Powertrain," [Tape 1 of 10], April 14, 1992 (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "First Interactive Management Workshop on Design of an Analytical Powertrain," [Tape 2 of 10], April 14, 1992 (Box 55, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "First Interactive Management Workshop on Design of an Analytical Powertrain," [Tape 3 of 10], April 14, 1992 (Box 56, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "First Interactive Management Workshop on Design of an Analytical Powertrain," [Tape 4 of 10], April 14, 1992 (Box 56, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "First Interactive Management Workshop on Design of an Analytical Powertrain," [Tape 5 of 10], April 15, 1992 (Box 56, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "First Interactive Management Workshop on Design of an Analytical Powertrain," [Tape 6 of 10], April 15, 1992 (Box 56, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "First Interactive Management Workshop on Design of an Analytical Powertrain," [Tape 7 of 10], April 15, 1992 (Box 56, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "First Interactive Management Workshop on Design of an Analytical Powertrain," [Tape 8 of 10], April 16, 1992 (Box 56, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "First Interactive Management Workshop on Design of an Analytical Powertrain," [Tape 9 of 10], April 16, 1992 (Box 56, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "First Interactive Management Workshop on Design of an Analytical Powertrain," [Tape 10 of 10] (Box 56, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 2)," [Tape 1 of 10], undated (Box 56, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 2)," [Tape 2 of 10], undated (Box 56, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 2)," [Tape 3 of 10], undated (Box 56, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 2)," [Tape 4 of 10], undated (Box 56, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 2)," [Tape 5 of 10], undated (Box 57, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 2)," [Tape 6 of 10], undated (Box 57, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 2)," [Tape 7 of 10], undated (Box 57, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 2)," [Tape 8 of 10], undated (Box 57, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 2)," [Tape 9 of 10], undated (Box 57, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 2)," [Tape 10 of 10], undated (Box 57, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 3)," [Tape 1 of 8], August 1992 (Box 57, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 3)," [Tape 2 of 8], August 1992 (Box 57, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 3)," [Tape 3 of 8], August 1992 (Box 57, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 3)," [Tape 4 of 8], August 1992 (Box 57, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 3)," [Tape 5 of 8], August 1992 (Box 57, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 3)," [Tape 6 of 8], August 1992 (Box 57, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 3)," [Tape 7 of 8], August 1992 (Box 57, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 3)," [Tape 8 of 8], August 1992 (Box 57, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Culture Seminar #1," on VHS Tape, August 1992 (Box 58, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 4)," [Tape 1 of 11], undated (Box 58, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 4)," [Tape 2 of 11], undated (Box 58, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 4)," [Tape 3 of 11], undated (Box 58, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 4)," [Tape 4 of 11], undated (Box 58, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 4)," [Tape 5 of 11], undated (Box 58, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 4)," [Tape 6 of 11], undated (Box 58, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 4)," [Tape 7 of 11], undated (Box 58, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 4)," [Tape 8 of 11], undated (Box 58, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 4)," [Tape 9 of 11], undated (Box 58, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 4)," [Tape 10 of 11], undated (Box 58, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop (A.P.T - 4)," [Tape 11 of 11], undated (Box 58, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Leadership & The Great University," (IASIS) Seminar Series, April 18, 1990 (Box 58, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Ford System Integration Workshops," Ford Motor Company [Tape 1 of 13], January 24, 1995 (Box 59, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Ford System Integration Workshops," Ford Motor Company [Tape 2 of 13], January 24, 1995 (Box 59, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Ford System Integration Workshops," Ford Motor Company [Tape 3 of 13], January 24, 1995 (Box 59, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Ford System Integration Workshops," Ford Motor Company [Tape 4 of 13], January 24, 1995 (Box 59, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Ford System Integration Workshops," Ford Motor Company [Tape 5 of 13], January 24, 1995 (Box 59, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Ford System Integration Workshops," Ford Motor Company [Tape 6 of 13], January 25, 1995 (Box 59, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Ford System Integration Workshops," Ford Motor Company [Tape 7 of 13], January 25, 1995 (Box 59, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Ford System Integration Workshops," Ford Motor Company [Tape 8 of 13], January 25, 1995 (Box 59, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Ford System Integration Workshops," Ford Motor Company [Tape 9 of 13], January 25, 1995 (Box 59, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Ford System Integration Workshops," Ford Motor Company [Tape 10 of 13], January 26, 1995 (Box 59, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Ford System Integration Workshops," Ford Motor Company [Tape 11 of 13], January 26, 1995 (Box 59, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Ford System Integration Workshops," Ford Motor Company [Tape 12 of 13], January 26, 1995 (Box 59, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Ford System Integration Workshops," Ford Motor Company [Tape 13 of 13], January 26, 1995 (Box 59, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Communication 531: Nominal Group Technique Session," George Mason University [Tape 1 of 1], February 8, 1988 (Box 60, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Communication 531: Nominal Group Technique Session," George Mason University [Tape 1 of 1], February 22, 1988 (Box 60, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Communication 531: Nominal Group Technique Session," George Mason University [Tape 1 of 1], March 21, 1988 (Box 60, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Design as a Group Process," Dr. Warfield George Mason Lecture Series," [Tape 1 of 1], July 13, 1987 (Box 60, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management Program: Consulting," [Tape 1 of 1], April 4, 1988 (Box 60, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Conflict Analysis & Resolution Course CONF 623, George Mason University," [Tape 1 of 5], January 29, 1987 (Box 60, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Conflict Analysis & Resolution Course CONF 623, George Mason University," [Tape 2 of 5], February 2, 1987 (Box 60, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Conflict Analysis & Resolution Course CONF 623, George Mason University," [Tape 3 of 5], February 12, 1987 (Box 60, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Conflict Analysis & Resolution Course CONF 623, George Mason University," [Tape 4 of 5], February 19, 1987 (Box 60, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Conflict Analysis & Resolution Course CONF 623, George Mason University," [Tape 5 of 5], March 19, 1987 (Box 60, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management Seminar: Dr. Guillermo Duenas", March 1, 1988 (Box 60, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management Seminar: Dr. John Nelson Warfield", March 23, 1988 (Box 60, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management Seminar: Dr. Hilda Blanco", February 18, 1988 (Box 60, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management Seminar: Dr. William Potapchuk", March 30, 1988 (Box 61, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management Seminar: Dr. Joseph Chilberg", December 9, 1987 (Box 61, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management Seminar: Professor Elohim's Talk", August 28, 1987 (Box 61, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management Seminar: Dr. James Laue", November 18, 1987 (Box 61, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management Seminar: Dr. Roger Volume", November 23, 1987 (Box 61, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Conflict Analysis Course CONF 623," Third Party Intervention in Conflict Resolution, November 20, 1986 (Box 61, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Conflict Analysis Course CONF 623," [Tape 1 of 2], March 5, 1987 (Box 61, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Conflict Analysis Course CONF 623," [Tape 2 of 2], March 5, 1987 (Box 61, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive MAnagement (C.I.M) Influences Seminar: Dr. John N. Warfield", March 3, 1987 (Box 61, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive MAnagement (C.I.M) Influences Seminar: Dr. John N. Warfield", 1986 (Box 61, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management (C.I.M) Influences Seminar: Dr. John N. Warfield", 1987 (Box 61, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive MAnagement (C.I.M) Influences Seminar: Dr. John N. Warfield", April 7, 1966 (Box 61, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management (C.I.M) Influences Seminar: Dr. John N. Warfield", April 14, 1987 (Box 61, Folder Videotape (VHS))
  - "Center for Interactive Management (C.I.M) Influences Seminar: Dr. John N. Warfield", March 31, 1987 (Box 61, Folder Videotape (VHS))